<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Ahmet Can Aydemir's Personal Blog RSS Feed]]></title><description><![CDATA[Personal website by Ahmet Can Aydemir.]]></description><link>https://ahmetcanaydemir.com</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 13:44:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[I Renewed My Personal Website]]></title><description><![CDATA[New things in the new year, so I started by renewing my website.]]></description><link>https://ahmetcanaydemir.com/renewed-my-personal-website/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://ahmetcanaydemir.com/renewed-my-personal-website/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ahmetcanaydemir.com/x/&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally I did it, I renewed my personal website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We entered the 2021, every new year people are in search of a change in their lives. For a long time, I have been thinking of renewing my website. I haven’t been blogging for a long time. Renewing my site can also be an important opportunity to start blogging. I’m not sure how much I can achieve, but this year I plan to focus more on blog posts, YouTube videos and open source projects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I published the previous version of this website in 2017 and I had almost never changed it. The site was Hugo-based and worked just fine. But I wanted to turn it into a React-based, minimal site that I know better the technology. It was not that difficult to do. &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/gaearon&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noopener noreferrer&quot;&gt;Dan Abramov&lt;/a&gt;’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/gaearon/overreacted.io&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noopener noreferrer&quot;&gt;overreacted.io&lt;/a&gt; project was based on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gatsbyjs.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noopener noreferrer&quot;&gt;Gatsby.js&lt;/a&gt; and I really liked its minimalism. I made some style changes for myself, added a few pages and the website you have seen now came out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On this website, I plan to write blogs in Turkish as well as in English. I know my English is not that good. Thus, I believe my English writing ability can improve. If you see any errors in my sentences, please write to me.&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;div style=&quot;margin-top=55px; font-style: italic;&quot;&gt;(This is an article posted to my blog at ahmetcanaydemir.com. You can read it online by &lt;a href=&quot;https://ahmetcanaydemir.com/renewed-my-personal-website/&quot;&gt;clicking here&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/div&gt;
              </content:encoded></item></channel></rss>